Muhammad Memon

Profile

Third Year Computer Engineering undergraduate student. A strong academic record and professional work ethic learning through various work experience and volunteering experiences. A passion for sports, problem-solving, and teamwork, and a computing person with excellent communication and computing skills and can work in Excel and Word and have independently with great experience in computers and work experiences. Love playing football & badminton and a passion in programming.

EDUCATION

2021 - Present	Technological	University	Dublin (TUD)	Dublin	Ireland
	1 Commono Sicur	CITIVELDIC	Daomi	100	, Daoini,	II CIUIIU

Bachelor of Computer engineering

GPA 3.47, 1st Class Honours (Expected)

Colaiste Phadraig Dublin, Ireland 2015 - 2021

LC – 563 points & JC – Ranked 79th percentile(4A's)

EXPERIENCE

Currys PcWorld Dublin, Ireland

Sales Assistant Feb 2023- July 2023

- Helping customers and reaching weekly targets for sales
- Handled daily Discount & Refund Logs
- Worked on customer satisfaction

Wowburger Dublin, Ireland

Supervisor July 2022- Jan 2023

- Handling a team of 15 staff members
- Make the weekly Rota and handle daily Discount & Refund Logs
- Working on Advertising & Marketing strategies

Memon Transport Limited Dublin, Ireland

Summer Analyst Jun 2020- July 2021

- Helped and sourced statements needed in depth Finance
- Developed knowledge in the areas of Tax and Banking
- Attended business strategy meetings with CEO

Leadership

Student Managed Fund Dublin, Ireland Sector Manager May 2022- Present

- Overseeing Consumer Staples Sector stocks
- •Leading a team of 10 young consumer junior analysts

Skills

BACK-END DEVELOPMENT | Java Python C/C++ FRONT END DEVELOPMENT | HTML CSS PHP PROGRAMMING TOOLS | GitHub, SQL **SOFTWARE PROFIENCY** | Microsoft Excel PowerPoint Word **PROFESSIONAL** | Problem Solving (Sales), Teamwork

ACHIEVEMENTS

Class Representative 1st year - TU Dublin Student Brand Ambassador - Deliveroo **Events Officer of Islamic Society - TU Dublin** Student Ambassador - Islamic Relief of Ireland